And we start by
defining a
function DFS that
takes a graph and a
starting vertex.
The graph is
represented as an
adjacency list
where each key is a
vertex and its
corresponding
value is a list of
its neighboring
vertices. We then
initialize two
sets visited to
keep track of
visited vertices
and result to
store the
traversal order.
We also create a
stack with the
starting vertex.
The main loop of
the algorithm is a
while loop that
continues until
the stack is
empty. In each
iteration, we pop
a vertex from the
stack and mark it
as visited. We
then append the
visited vertex to
the result list
and add its
unvisited
neighbors to the
stack. After the
loop, we return
the result list,
which contains
the traversal
order of the graph
using DFS. The
function will
return the BFS
traversal order
of the graph,
which is a correct
representation
of the graph
structure.