We start by
defining a
function called
bubble sort. That
takes an array as
an input. Then we
calculate the
length of the
input array and
store it in the
variable n. We use
two nested loops
to compare
adjacent
elements in the
array. The outer
loop iterates n
times, and the
inner loop
iterates ni1
times inside the
outer loop.
Inside the inner
loop, we compare
adjacent
elements. If the
current element
is greater than
the next element,
we swap them. This
process is called
a bubble because
the largest
element bubbles
up to the end of the
array in each
iteration. After
one iteration of
the outer loop,
the largest
element is placed
at the end of the
array. We repeat
the process until
the entire array
is sorted.
Finally, we
return the sorted
array.