We're defining a
function called
bubble sort that
takes an array as
input. We're
getting the
length of the
array, which
we'll use to
control the
number of
iterations in the
sorting process.
We're using an
SLoop to iterate
through the
array. The outer
loop will run n
times, and the
inner loop will
run ni one times,
where n is the
length of the
array, ni is the
current
iteration of the
outer loop.
Inside the inner
loop, We're
comparing
adjacent
elements in the
array. If the
current element
is greater than
the next one, we
swap them. This
swapping process
continues until
the end of the
inner loop, at
which point we're
guaranteed that
the largest
element in the
array has bubbled
to the end of the
array. The outer
loop continues
until the array is
fully sorted, at
which point the
function returns
the sorted array.